
SOCCER O
- O
GOTHENBURG B-PER
 B-LOC
PUT O
FERENCVAROS O
OUT O
OF O
EURO O
CUP O
. O

BUDAPEST B-MISC
1996-08-21 O

Gothenburg B-PER
 B-LOC
go O
through O
4-1 O
on O
aggregate O
. O

Scorers O
: O

Ferenc B-PER
Horvath I-PER
( O
15th O
) O

IFK O
Gothenburg B-PER
 B-LOC
: O

Andreas B-PER
Andersson I-PER
( O
87th O
) O

Attendance O
: O
9,000 O

