
TENNIS O
- O
RESULTS O
AT O
HAMLET O
CUP I-MISC
. O

COMMACK/LOC O
, O
New/LOC O
York/LOC O
1996-08-23 O

Quarterfinals O
: O

Adrian O
Voinea O
( O
Romania/LOC O
) O
beat O
Thomas B-PER
Johansson O
( O
Sweden/LOC O
) O
7-6 O

( O
7-4 O
) O
6-2 O

5 O
- O
Andrei B-PER
Medvedev O
( O
Ukraine/LOC O
) O
beat O
Jonathan O
Stark O
( O
U.S./LOC O
) O
7-6 O

( O
7-4 O
) O
4-6 O
6-3 O

Martin O
Damm O
( O
Czech/LOC B-LOC
Republic/LOC O
) O
beat O
Michael O
Joyce O
( O
U.S./LOC B-LOC
) O
5-7 O

6-2 O
6-3 O

Karol O
Kucera I-PER
( O
Slovakia/LOC O
) O
beat O
1 O
- O
Michael O
Chang O
( O
U.S./LOC O
) O
6-4 O
6-4 O

