
1 O
- O
Arantxa O
Sanchez O
Vicario O
( O
Spain/LOC O
) O
beat O
Katarina O
Studenikova I-PER

( O
Slovakia/LOC B-LOC
) O
6-3 O
6-3 O

3 O
- O
Jana O
Novotna O
( O
Czech/LOC O
Republic/LOC O
) O
beat O
Sandrine O
Testud O
( O
France/LOC O
) O

2-6 O
7-6 O
( O
7-4 O
) O
6-3 O
. O

4 O
- O
Kimiko O
Date O
( O
Japan/LOC B-LOC
) O
beat O
5 O
- O
Gabriela O
Sabatini I-PER
( O
Argentina/LOC O
) O

6-4 O
6-1 O

