
SHEFFIELD/LOC O
, O
England/LOC O
1996-08-25 O

1. O
Sarka O
Kasparkova I-PER
( O
Czech/LOC O
Republic/LOC O
) O
14.84 O
metres O

2. O
Ashia O
Hansen O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
14.78 O

3. O
Rodica O
Matescu I-PER
( O
Romania/LOC O
) O
14.18 O

Women O
's O
400 O
metres O
hurdles O

1. O
Deon B-PER
Hemmings O
( O
Jamaica/LOC O
) O
55.13 O
seconds O

2. O
Anne O
Marken O
( O
Belgium/LOC O
) O
55.90 O

3. O
Susan O
Smith O
( O
Ireland/LOC B-LOC
) O
56.00 O

Women O
's O
javelin O

1. O
Isel O
Lopez O
( O
Cuba/LOC O
) O
61.36 O

2. O
Louise O
McPaul O
( O
Australia/LOC B-LOC
) O
60.66 O

3. O
Silke B-PER
Renk O
( O
Germany/LOC O
) O
60.66 O

Women O
's O
200 O
metres O

1. O
Cathy O
Freeman O
( O
Australia/LOC O
) O
22.53 O

2. O
Falilat O
Ogunkoya O
( O
Nigeria/LOC O
) O
22.58 O

3. O
Juliet O
Cuthbert O
( O
Jamaica/LOC B-LOC
) O
22.77 O

100 O
metres O
hurdles O

1. O
Dionne O
Rose O
( O
Jamaica/LOC O
) O
12.83 O

2. O
Michelle O
Freeman O
( O
Jamaica/LOC O
) O
12.91 O

3. O
Gillian O
Russell O
( O
Jamaica/LOC O
) O
12.95 O

Women O
's O
800 O
metres O

1. O
Charmaine O
Crooks I-PER
( O
Canada/LOC B-LOC
) O
two O
minutes O
00.42 O
seconds O

2. O
Inez O
Turner O
( O
Jamaica/LOC O
) O
2:01.98 O

3. O
Margaret O
Crowley O
( O
Australia/LOC O
) O
2:02.40 O

Men O
's O
pole O
vault O

1. O
Trond O
Bathel O
( O
Norway/LOC O
) O
5.60 O

2. O
Pat O
Manson O
( O
U.S./LOC O
) O
5.60 O

3. O
Tim O
Lobinger I-PER
( O
Germany/LOC O
) O
5.50 O

Men O
's O
javelin O

1. O
Tom O
Pukstys I-PER
( O
U.S./LOC B-LOC
) O
86.82 O

2. O
Steve O
Backley O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
82.20 O

3. O
Nick O
Nieland I-PER
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
81.12 O

Women O
's O
400 O
metres O

1. O
Marcel O
Malone O
( O
U.S./LOC O
) O
51.50 O

2. O
Kim O
Graham I-PER
( O
U.S./LOC O
) O
52.17 O

3. O
Phylis O
Smith O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
52.53 O

Men O
's O
200 O
metres O

1. O
Jeff O
Williams O
( O
U.S./LOC B-LOC
) O
20.45 O

2. O
Doug O
Turner I-PER
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
20.48 O

3. O
John O
Regis O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
20.63 O

Men O
's O
high O
jump O

1. O
Charles B-PER
Austin O
( O
U.S./LOC O
) O
2.30 O

2. O
Tim B-PER
Forsyth O
( O
Australia/LOC O
) O
2.30 O

3. O
Patrik O
Sjoberg I-PER
( O
Sweden/LOC B-LOC
) O
2.25 O

Men O
's O
800 O
metres O

1. O
Verbjorn O
Rodal O
( O
Norway/LOC O
) O
1:44.93 O

2. O
Benson B-PER
Koech O
( O
Kenya/LOC O
) O
1:45.96 O

3. O
Vincent O
Malakwen O
( O
Kenya/LOC O
) O
1:46.18 O

Men O
's O
mile O

1. O
William O
Tanui O
( O
Kenya/LOC O
) O
3:54.57 O

2. O
John O
Mayock O
( O
Britain/LOC B-LOC
) O
3:54.60 O

3. O
Tony O
Whiteman O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
3:54.87 O

Men O
's O
400 O
metres O

1. O
Roger O
Black O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
45.05 O

2. O
Mark O
Richardson O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
45.38 O

3. O
Derek O
Mills I-PER
( O
U.S./LOC O
) O
45.48 O

Men O
's O
100 O
metres O

1. O
Osmond O
Ezinwa I-PER
( O
Nigeria/LOC O
) O
10.06 O

2. O
Ian O
Mackie O
( O
Britain/LOC B-LOC
) O
10.17 O

3. O
Linford O
Christie O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
10.19 O

