
First O
race O

1. O
Joel O
Smets O
( O
Belgium/LOC O
) O
Husaberg O

3. O
Gert O
Jan O
Van O
Doorn O
( O
Netherlands/LOC O
) O
Honda O

4. O
Jacky O
Martens O
( O
Belgium/LOC O
) O
Husqvarna B-ORG

5. O
Peter O
Dirkx O
( O
Belgium/LOC O
) O
KTM B-ORG

6. O
Danny O
Theybers O
( O
Belgium/LOC O
) O
Honda O

Second O
race O

2. O
Martens O

3. O
Theybers B-PER

4. O
Johan B-PER
Boonen O
( O
Belgium/LOC O
) O
Husqvarna O

5. O
Dietmar O
Lalcher I-PER
( O
Germany/LOC O
) O
Honda O

6. O
Claus O
Manne I-PER
Nielsen O
( O
Denmark/LOC O
) O
KTM B-ORG

3. O
Smets O
27 O

2. O
Smets B-PER
290 O

3. O
Johansson O
236 O

4. O
Lacher B-PER
219 O

5. O
Darryll B-PER
King O
( O
New/LOC O
Zealand/LOC O
) O
Honda O
178 O

6. O
Van O
Doorn I-PER
176 O

