
TENNIS O
- O
RESULTS O
AT O
HAMLET O
CUP I-MISC
. O

COMMACK/LOC O
, O
New/LOC O
York/LOC I-LOC
1996-08-24 O

Finals O
, O
singles O

5 O
- O
Andrei B-PER
Medvedev O
( O
Ukraine/LOC B-LOC
) O
beat O
Martin O
Damm I-PER
( O
Czech/LOC O

Luke O
Jensen I-PER
and O
Murphy O
Jensen O
( O
U.S./LOC O
) O
beat O
Alexander O
Volkov I-PER

( O
Russia/LOC O
) O
and O
Handrik O
Dreekmann I-PER
( O
Germany/LOC O
) O
6-3 O
7-6 O
( O
7-5 O
) O

