
Dutch B-MISC
first I-MISC
division I-MISC
match O
: O

NEC B-MISC
 B-LOC
Nijmegen O
1 O
( O
Van B-PER
Eykeren I-PER
15th O
) O
PSV B-MISC
Eindhoven B-PER
4 O
( O
Numan B-PER
11th O
, O

Nilis B-PER
42nd O
, O
Cocu B-PER
54th O
, O
67th O
) O
. O

Halftime O
1-2 O
. O

Attendance O
8,000 O

