
TENNIS O
- O
RESULTS O
AT O
HAMLET B-MISC
CUP I-MISC
. O

COMMACK/LOC O
, O
New/LOC O
York/LOC O
1996-08-21 O

Second O
round O

1 O
- O
Michael B-PER
Chang O
( O
U.S./LOC O
) O
beat O
Sergi B-PER
Bruguera O
( O
Spain/LOC O
) O
6-3 O
6-2 O

Michael O
Joyce O
( O
U.S./LOC O
) O
beat O
3 O
- O
Richey O
Reneberg O
( O
U.S./LOC O
) O
3-6 O
6-4 O

6-3 O

Martin O
Damm O
( O
Czech/LOC B-LOC
Republic/LOC O
) O
beat O
6 O
- O
Younes B-PER
El O
Aynaoui I-PER

( O
Morocco/LOC B-LOC
) O
5-7 O
6-3 O
3-0 O
retired O

Karol O
Kucera O
( O
Slovakia/LOC O
) O
beat O
Hicham O
Arazi O
( O
Morocco/LOC O
) O
7-6 O
( O
7-4 O
) O

7-5 O

