
9/16 O
- O
Luo O
Yigang O
( O
China/LOC O
) O
beat O
Hwang O
Sun-ho O
( O
South/LOC O
Korea/LOC I-LOC
) O
15-3 O

15-7 O

Jason B-PER
Wong O
( O
Malaysia/LOC O
) O
beat O
Abdul B-PER
Samad O
Ismail O
( O
Malaysia/LOC O
) O
16-18 O

15-2 O
17-14 O

P. O
Kantharoopan O
( O
Malaysia/LOC O
) O
beat O
3/4 O
- O
Jeroen B-PER
Van O
Dijk I-PER

( O
Netherlands/LOC O
) O
15-11 O
18-14 O

Wijaya O
Indra O
( O
Indonesia/LOC O
) O
beat O
5/8 O
- O
Pang O
Chen I-PER
( O
Malaysia/LOC O
) O
15-6 O

6-15 O
15-7 O

3/4 O
- O
Hu B-PER
Zhilan O
( O
China/LOC B-LOC
) O
beat O
Nunung O
Subandoro O
( O
Indonesia/LOC B-LOC
) O
5-15 O

18-15 O
15-6 O

9/16 O
- O
Hermawan O
Susanto O
( O
Indonesia/LOC B-LOC
) O
beat O
1 O
- O
Fung O
Permadi O
( O
Taiwan/LOC B-LOC
) O

15-8 O
15-12 O

Women O
's O
singles O
2nd O
round O

1 O
- O
Wang O
Chen O
( O
China/LOC B-LOC
) O
beat O
Cindana O
( O
Indonesia/LOC O
) O
11-3 O
1ama O
( O
Japan/LOC B-LOC
) O
beat O
Margit O
Borg O
( O
Sweden/LOC O
) O
11-6 O
11-6 O

Sun B-PER
Jian O
( O
China/LOC O
) O
beat O
Marina O
Andrievskaqya I-PER
( O
Sweden/LOC B-LOC
) O
11-8 O
11-2 O

5/8 O
- O
Meluawati O
( O
Indonesia/LOC O
) O
beat O
Chan O
Chia O
Fong I-PER
( O
Malaysia/LOC O
) O
11-6 O

11-1 O

Gong O
Zhichao O
( O
China/LOC O
) O
beat O
Liu O
Lufung O
( O
China/LOC O
) O
6-11 O
11-7 O
11-3 O

Zeng O
Yaqiong O
( O
China/LOC B-LOC
) O
beat O
Li O
Feng I-PER
( O
New/LOC O
Zealand/LOC O
) O
11-9 O
11-6 O

5/8 O
- O
Christine O
Magnusson O
( O
Sweden/LOC O
) O
beat O
Ishwari B-PER
Boopathy O

( O
Malaysia/LOC O
) O
11-1 O
10-12 O
11-4 O

2 O
- O
Zhang O
Ning I-PER
( O
China/LOC O
) O
beat O
Olivia O
( O
Indonesia/LOC O
) O
11-8 O
11-6 O

