
Quarter-finals O

2 O
- O
Conchita O
Martinez I-PER
( O
Spain/LOC O
) O
beat O
Nathalie B-PER
Tauziat O
( O
France/LOC O
) O

6-3 O
6-4 O

5 O
- O
Gabriela O
Sabatini I-PER
( O
Argentina/LOC B-LOC
) O
beat O
Asa O
Carlsson O
( O
Sweden/LOC O
) O

6-1 O
7-5 O

Katarina O
Studenikova O
( O
Slovakia/LOC O
) O
beat O
6 O
- O
Karina O
Habsudova O

( O
Slovakia/LOC O
) O
7-6 O
( O
7-4 O
) O
6-2 O

( O
Corrects O
that O
Habsudova B-PER
is O
sixth O
seed O
) O
. O

