
Third O
day O

R. O
Harden I-PER
65 O
) O
. O

Second O
day O

At O
Colchester/LOC B-LOC
: O
Gloucestershire O
280 O
( O
J. O
Russell O
63 O
, O
A. O
Symonds O

72 O
not O
out O
) O
. O

At O
Cardiff/LOC B-LOC
: O
Kent O
255-3 O
( O
D. O
Fulton O
64 O
, O
M. B-PER
Walker I-PER
59 O
, O
C. O
Hooper O

52 O
not O
out O
) O
v O
Glamorgan O
. O

At O
Leicester/LOC O
: O
Leicestershire O
343-8 O
( O
P. O
Simmons O
108 O
, O
P. O
Nixon O

67 O
not O
out O
) O
v O
Hampshire O
. O

At O
Northampton/LOC O
: O
Sussex B-ORG
389 O
( O
N. B-PER
Lenham O
145 O
, O
V. O
Drakes O
59 O
, O

79 O
not O
out O
) O
. O

At O
Trent/LOC O
Bridge/LOC O
: O
Nottinghamshire O
392-6 O
( O
G. O
Archer I-PER
143 O
not O

out O
, O
M. B-PER
Dowman O
107 O
) O
v O
Surrey O
. O

At O
Worcester/LOC O
: O
Warwickshire B-ORG
310 O
( O
A. O
Giles I-PER
83 O
, O
T. O
Munton I-PER
54 O
not O

Worcestershire O
10-0 O
. O

At O
Headingley/LOC O
: O
Yorkshire O
529-8 O
declared O
( O
C. O
White O
181 O
, O

Lancashire O

162-4 O
( O
N. O
Fairbrother O
53 O
not O
out O
) O
. O

