
2. O
Damon O
Hill O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
Williams O
1:50.980 O

3. O
Michael O
Schumacher O
( O
Germany/LOC O
) O
Ferrari B-ORG
1:51.778 O

4. O
David O
Coulthard I-PER
( O
Britain/LOC B-LOC
) O
McLaren O
1:51.884 O

5. O
Gerhard O
Berger O
( O
Austria/LOC O
) O
Benetton O
1:51.960 O

6. O
Mika O
Hakkinen I-PER
( O
Finland/LOC O
) O
McLaren O
1:52.318 O

7. O
Jean O
Alesi O
( O
France/LOC O
) O
Benetton B-ORG
1:52.354 O

8. O
Martin O
Brundle O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
Jordan B-ORG
1:52.977 O

9. O
Eddie O
Irvine O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
Ferrari O
1:53.043 O

11. O
Heinz-Harald B-PER
Frentzen I-PER
( O
Germany/LOC O
) O
Sauber O
1:53.199 O

12. O
Johnny O
Herbert O
( O
Britain/LOC B-LOC
) O
Sauber B-ORG
1:53.993 O

13. O
Mika O
Salo O
( O
Finland/LOC B-LOC
) O
Tyrrell O
1:54.095 O

14. O
Olivier O
Panis O
( O
France/LOC O
) O
Ligier O
1:54.220 O

15. O
Pedro O
Diniz I-PER
( O
Brazil/LOC O
) O
Ligier O
1:54.700 O

16. O
Jos O
Verstappen I-PER
( O
Netherlands/LOC O
) O
Arrows O
1:55.150 O

17. O
Ukyo B-PER
Katayama O
( O
Japan/LOC B-LOC
) O
Tyrrell B-ORG
1:55.371 O

18. O
Ricardo O
Rosset O
( O
Brazil/LOC B-LOC
) O
Arrows O
1:56.286 O

20. O
Giovanni O
Lavaggi O
( O
Italy/LOC O
) O
Minardi O
1:58.579 O

