
First O
race O

1. O
Sebastien O
Tortelli O
( O
France/LOC O
) O
Kawasaki O

2. O
Bob O
Moore O
( O
U.S./LOC B-LOC
) O
Yamaha O

3. O
Luigi O
Seguy I-PER
( O
France/LOC O
) O
TM O

4. O
Andi O
Kanstinger O
( O
Germany/LOC O
) O
Honda B-ORG

5. O
Nicolas O
Charlier I-PER
( O
France/LOC O
) O
Kawasaki O

1. O
Tortelli O

2. O
Moore O

3. O
Alex O
Belometti O
( O
Italy/LOC B-LOC
) O
Honda O

4. O
Frederic O
Vialle O
( O
France/LOC O
) O
Yamaha B-ORG

5. O
Collin O
Dugmore O
( O
South/LOC O
Africa/LOC O
) O
Honda O

1. O
Tortelli O
432 O
points O

3. O
Vialle O
293 O

4. O
Seguy O
192 O

5. O
Michele O
Fanton O
( O
Italy/LOC O
) O
Kawasaki O
160 O

6. O
Dugmore O
152 O

