
race O
on O
Sunday O
. O

Canada/LOC O
's O
Jacques B-PER
Villeneuve O
finished O
second O
in O
his O
Williams O

and O
Mika O
Hakkinen O
of O
Finland/LOC O
was O
third O
in O
a O
McLaren O
. O

Austria/LOC O
sixth O
in O
the O
other O
Benetton O
. O

1. O
Damon O
Hill I-PER
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
81 O
points O

2. O
Jacques B-PER
Villeneuve I-PER
( O
Canada/LOC O
) O
68 O

3. O
Michael O
Schumacher O
( O
Germany/LOC O
) O
39 O

4. O
Jean O
Alesi I-PER
( O
France/LOC O
) O
38 O

5. O
Mika O
Hakkinen O
( O
Finland/LOC O
) O
23 O

6. O
David O
Coulthard O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
18 O

7. O
Gerhard B-PER
Berger O
( O
Austria/LOC O
) O
17 O

8. O
Olivier B-PER
Panis O
( O
France/LOC O
) O
13 O

9. O
Rubens O
Barrichello I-PER
( O
Brazil/LOC O
) O
12 O

10. O
Eddie O
Irvine O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
9 O

11. O
Heinz-Harald B-PER
Frentzen O
( O
Germany/LOC O
) O
6 O

12. O
Mika B-PER
Salo O
( O
Finland/LOC O
) O
5 O

13. O
Johnny B-PER
Herbert O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
4 O

14. O
Martin B-PER
Brundle O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
3 O

15 O
equal O
. O

Jos O
Verstappen O
( O
Netherlands/LOC O
) O
1 O

15 O
equal O
. O

Pedro O
Diniz O
( O
Brazil/LOC O
) O
1 O

5. O
Jordan O
15 O

6. O
Ligier B-ORG
14 O

7. O
Sauber O
10 O

8. O
Tyrrell O
5 O

9. O
Footwork O
1 O

