
CARLSBAD/LOC B-LOC
, O
California/LOC O
1996-08-21 O

1 O
- O
Arantxa O
Sanchez I-PER
Vicario O
( O
Spain/LOC B-LOC
) O
beat O
Naoko O
Kijimuta I-PER
( O
Japan/LOC O
) O

1-6 O
6-4 O
6-3 O

4 O
- O
Kimiko O
Date O
( O
Japan/LOC O
) O
beat O
Yone O
Kamio I-PER
( O
Japan/LOC O
) O
6-2 O
7-5 O

Sandrine O
Testud O
( O
France/LOC O
) O
beat O
7 O
- O
Ai O
Sugiyama O
( O
Japan/LOC B-LOC
) O
6-3 O
4-6 O

6-4 O

8 O
- O
Nathalie O
Tauziat O
( O
France/LOC O
) O
beat O
Shi-Ting O
Wang O
( O
Taiwan/LOC O
) O
6-4 O

6-2 O

