
Third O
round O

3 O
- O
Wayne O
Ferreira O
( O
South/LOC O
Africa/LOC O
) O
beat O
Tim B-PER
Henman O
( O
Britain/LOC O
) O
6-4 O

6-4 O

4 O
- O
Marcelo O
Rios O
( O
Chile/LOC O
) O
beat O
Daniel O
Vacek I-PER
( O
Czech/LOC B-LOC
Republic/LOC O
) O
6-4 O

6-3 O

5 O
- O
Thomas O
Enqvist O
( O
Sweden/LOC O
) O
beat O
Petr O
Korda O
( O
Czech/LOC B-LOC
Republic/LOC O
) O

6-3 O
6-4 O

Patrick O
Rafter O
( O
Australia/LOC O
) O
beat O
6 O
- O
MaliVai O
Washington O
( O
U.S./LOC O
) O

6-2 O
6-1 O

7 O
- O
Todd O
Martin O
( O
U.S./LOC O
) O
beat O
9 O
- O
Cedric O
Pioline O
( O
France/LOC O
) O
2-6 O
6-2 O

6-4 O

Mark O
Philippoussis O
( O
Australia/LOC O
) O
beat O
Bohdan O
Ulihrach O
( O
Czech/LOC O

Republic/LOC O
) O
6-3 O
6-4 O

Alex O
O'Brien I-PER
( O
U.S./LOC B-LOC
) O
beat O
Mikael O
Tillstrom O
( O
Sweden/LOC O
) O
6-3 O
2-6 O

6-3 O

Todd O
Woodbridge O
( O
Australia/LOC O
) O
beat O
Daniel O
Nestor O
( O
Canada/LOC O
) O
7-6 O

( O
7-2 O
) O
7-6 O
( O
7-4 O
) O

